My story begins in London...
我的故事始于伦敦
not so very long ago.
就在不久以前
Yet so much has happened since then, that it seems like an eternity.
发生的事让我永生难忘
At that time, I lived with my pet...
那个时候,我和我的宠物一起住在...
in a bachelor flat just off Regents Park.
摄政王公园附近的 一家单身公寓里
It was a beautiful spring day,
那是一个美丽的春天
a tedious time of the year for bachelors.
对单身汉来说 一年里最单调乏味的日子
Oh... that's my pet, Roger Radcliff,
哦... 这就是我的宠物 罗杰 雷德克里夫
a musician of sorts.
一种叫“音乐家”的品种
I'm the one with the spots.
我呢,是那种带斑点的品种
My name's Pongo.
我叫 庞戈
As far as I could see,
在我看来
the old notion that a bachelor's life was so...
那些鼓吹单身生活是如何如何...
glamorous and carefree was all nonsense.
迷人和自由的老套说辞 其实都是胡说八道
It was downright dull.
其实它真是无聊之极
It was plain to see that my old pet needed someone.
很明显,我的老家伙需要... 另一半
But if it were left up to Roger, we'd be bachelors forever.
但是如果打算靠 罗杰, 那我们只有永远打光棍
He was married to his work, writing songs.
他早就和他的工作结了婚 而他的工作就是写歌
Songs about romance... of all things,
特别是那种浪漫的情歌...
something he knew absolutely nothing about.
可惜他完全不了解那东西
Oh, he's intelligent enough, as humans go.
嗯, 以人类的标准而言,他有那么聪明
And I think you could say, Roger is a rather handsome animal in his way.
而且我想 罗杰也说得上是一只英俊的动物
I could see no reason why my pet...
我实在搞不懂 为什么我这个宠物...
didn't deserve an attractive mate.
会找不到般配的伴侣
At least I was determined to do my best.
至少我正尽所能地帮忙
Of course, dogs are a pretty poor judge of human beauty.
当然啦,狗不怎么能评判 人类的美丑
But I had a rough idea...
但我还是有一个大体的概念...
of what to look for.
对于我想要的那种类型
Hmm! Unusual breed.
嗯! 不太寻常的品种
Very unusual.
非常不寻常哦
Hmm! Oh, surely not.
哼! 绝对不是这一种
Well now, what have we here?
哦, 瞧我看到什么了?
Hmm.
嗯.
Well, a little... too short coupled.
得, 一种小脚短腿的
Nope!
不妙!
I say! Well, I do say!
瞧啊! 好好瞧瞧!
Now there's a fancy breed.
这对倒是很时髦的品种哦
Hmm. Perhaps a little too fancy.
呃. 也许太时髦了一点
Yes, much too fancy.
真的, 太时髦了
Too old. Too young.
太老了 太嫩了
It was a problem, a realproblem.
真是个大难题啊
Well, now that's a bit more like it!
啊哈, 这个比较像样点!
The most beautiful creature on four legs!
一只最美丽的四脚动物!
Now if only the girl...
哦, 如果那女孩...
Well! She's very lovely too.
哈! 她也非常可爱
It was almost too good to be true.
简直太完美了
I'd never find another pair like that,
再也找不到这么好的一对了
not if I looked for 100 years.
哪怕我再找一百年
Ah, they're heading for the park.
啊, 她们朝公园走去了
A perfect meeting place... if I can only arrange it.
很不错的约会地点... 如果我好好地安排一下
Uh-oh... but Roger never stopped work 'til after 5:00.
糟了... 罗杰 不到5点 是不会停工的
That would be too late.
那时可就太晚了
After 5:00 already.
已经过5点了
Fancy that.
我看到了
All right, Pongo. All right, boy.
好了,庞戈. 好吧, 小伙计
Pongo, boy, take it easy!
庞戈, 小伙子 放轻松点!
What's all the hurry?
干嘛这么急呢?
Pongo, boy, slow down.
庞戈, 伙计, 慢点儿
I was afraid we'd missed them.
我真怕我们已经错过她们了
Perhaps they passed on by the park.
也许她们穿过公园直接走了
Then suddenly... I spotted them.
忽然之间... 我发现了她们
It was a perfect situation if I plannedit right.
这是个十全十美的状况 假如我计划正确的话
I couldn't depend on Roger. I knew what he'd do.
罗杰 是指望不上了 我很清楚他会干啥
He'd settle on the grass, puff his pipe and that would be it.
他只会坐在草地上抽他的烟斗
No, it was all up to me.
唉, 只有靠我了
Well.
好吧
At first I had no particular plan,
刚开始, 我也想不出什么好点子
just anything to attract attention.
但至少得引起人家的注意
You know, stir things up a bit.
好咧 小小地惹是生非一下
Pongo, you silly old thing!
庞戈, 你这老小子
C'm on! C'm on, let's have it, boy.
来! 把帽子还我吧, 小伙子
Pongo!
庞戈!
For a while, it seemed to work.
效果不错
At least they had seen one another.
至少他们都看见了对方
Things were going along first-rate.
看来事情可以迅速地发展下去
But for some strange reason they left!
可是因为某种奇特的原因 她们走了!
C'mon, you old renegade. We're going home.
来吧, 你这老叛徒 我们该回家了
But I wasn't giving up.
可我是不会放弃的
I was determined that somehow they just had to meet.
我决定无论如何 都要让他们再碰面
- Oh! - Ohhh!
- 哦! - 啊!
I beg your pardon. Please excuse me.
我得求您原谅 请原谅我吧
I must say, what on earth!
这究竟是... 怎么回事?!
- Oh, really. Good heavens. - Oh, dear.
- 哦, 主啊! - 哦, 天哪
- Ohh! - Ahh, ahh!
- 哦! - 啊呀!
Oh, oh.
哦
Oh, my new spring suit and my new hat!
哦, 我的新春套装 还有我的新帽子!
Ah, ah... I'm terribly sorry.
哎呀... 我真的是很抱歉
Please let me help you.
请允许我来帮你一把
I'm so sorry.
真是对不起
I don't know what's come over him.
我不知道这家伙是怎么了
I'm so sorry. He's never acted this way before.
非常抱歉. 他以前从来没这么乱来过
Please, just go away. You've done enough.
拜托你走吧 你做的够多的了
Please? Oh.
拜托... 哦
Oh, I say. Here, take mine.
哦, 没问题 这儿, 用我的吧
Oh.
呃
Wilt thou love her, comfort her,
你是否愿意爱她, 安慰她,
honour and keep her in sickness and in health;
尊敬她, 保护她 无论是病痛还是健康
and forsaking all others,
无论生活是好是坏
keep thee only unto her so long as ye both shall live?
在你有生之年照顾她?
I will.
我愿意
For the first six months or so...
前六个月里...
we lived in a small house near the park,
我们住在公园附近的一栋小房子里
a modest little place...
一间很普通的小房子...
but just right for two couples who were just starting out.
不过正适合我们这两对新婚夫妇
Perdita, darling, are you all right?
佩蒂塔, 亲爱的 你没事吧?
Oh, of course, dear.
哦, 当然, 亲爱的
After all, dogs were having puppies long before our time.
毕竟怀孕的时候比较容易疲倦
Oh, that's Nanny, a wonderful cook and housekeeper.
哦, 那是奶妈 一位好厨师和好管家
She's such a kind, understanding soul.
她非常地和谐, 体贴他人
You know,
你知道吗
at times she seems almost canine.
有时候她还真象我们的同类
Roger, dear,
罗杰, 亲爱的
tea time.
午茶时间到了
Tea time!
午茶时间!
Melody first, my dear.
先有美妙的旋律, 我亲爱的
And then the lyrics, hmm?
然后再填词, 懂吗?
Oh, Pongo... it's her. It's that devil woman.
哦, 庞戈... 是她 是那个坏女人
Oh, must be Cruella, your dearly devoted old schoolmate.
啊, 一定是 克鲁拉 你那死党兼老同学
Cruella de Vil.
克鲁拉 德 威尔
That's it!
我想到了!
- Oh, Roger.
- 哦, 罗杰 你真是...
Ohh!
哦!
Roger, she'll hear you.
罗杰, 她会听见的
Let her in, Nanny.
请她进来, 奶妈
- Anita, darling! - How are you?
- 安妮塔, 亲爱的! - 你好吗?
Miserable as usual. Perfectly wretched!
和以往一样糟糕 简直糟透了!
Where are they? Where are they?
它们在哪儿? 它们在哪儿?
For heaven sakes, where are they?
老天爷, 它们到底在哪儿?
- Who, Cruella? - The puppies! The puppies.
- 谁呀, 克鲁拉? - 小狗啊! 那些小狗
No time for games. Where are the little brutes?
没时间开玩笑了 那些小畜生在哪?
It'll be at least three weeks. No rushing these things.
哦, 至少还要等三个星期呢 这种事急不得的
Anita, you're such a wit.
安妮塔, 你还真风趣
Here, dog, here.
来这儿, 小狗狗, 这儿来
Here, dog.
来这儿, 小狗狗
Cruella, isn't that a new fur coat?
克鲁拉, 你又换了件新的皮裘大衣?
My only true love, darling.
这不过是我唯一的嗜好, 亲爱的
I live for furs. I worship furs!
我为皮裘而生 我崇拜皮裘!
Is there a woman in this wretched worldw ho doesn't?
住在这个悲惨世界里的女人 哪一个不喜欢皮裘?
Oh, I'd like a nice fur,
哦, 我也喜欢皮裘
but there are many other thing...
但是生活里还有许多其它的东西...
Sweet, simple Anita.
可爱的, 天真的 安妮塔.
I know, I know!
我知道, 我知道!
This horrid little house is your dream castle.
这栋破烂小楼就是你的梦幻城堡
And poor Roger is your bold and fearless Sir Galahad!
而可怜的 罗杰 就是你鲁莽、无畏的白马王子!
Oh, Cruella.
哦, 克鲁拉
Then of course you have your little spotted friends.
当然啦, 还有你的小斑点朋友们
Oh yes,
是啊
I must say... such perfectly beautiful coats.
我得说... 非常美丽的毛皮
- Won't you have some tea? - I've got to run.
- 你要不要来点热茶? - 我得走了
Let me know when the puppies arrive.
生小狗的时候告诉我一声
- You will, won't you, dear? - Yes, Cruella.
- 你会吗, 亲爱的? - 好的, 克鲁拉
Don't forget, it's a promise. See you in three weeks.
别忘了, 你答应过我的. 三礼拜以后再见
Cheerio, darling.
加油干吧, 我亲爱的朋友
Ohh!
哦!
You're no help.
真拿你没办法
Roger, you are an idiot!
罗杰, 你就会瞎扯
- Perdy? - That witch. That devil woman.
- 佩蒂? - 那个巫婆, 那个坏女人
She wants our puppies. That's all she's after.
她想要我们的孩子 她的目的就是这个
Don't worry, Perdy. They're on to her.
别担心, 佩蒂. 他们能应付她的
Nothing's going to happen to our puppies.
我们的孩子会平安无事的
What does she want with them?
她要孩子们是想干嘛?
She can't possibly love them.
她不可能会爱他们
Oh, Pongo.
哦, 庞戈
I was so happy at first, but now I...
起初我是那么地高兴 可是现在我...
Oh, I...
哦, 我...
I wish we weren't having any.
我倒宁愿我们没有孩子
Poor Perdita. Of course, she had no choice.
可怜的 佩蒂塔 当然, 她也没得选择
The puppies arrived right on schedule...
小狗狗们如期出生...
one wild and stormy night in October.
在十月的一个狂风暴雨的夜晚
Ohh!
哦!
Steady, boy.
稳着点, 伙计
The puppies are here!
小狗狗们出生了!
Oh... the puppies are here!
哦...小狗狗生下来了!
How many?
多少只?
- Eight. - Eight?
- 八只 - 八只?
By George, Pongo! Eight puppies.
太棒了, 庞戈! 八只小狗狗
Ten.
十只
- Eleven. - Eleven.
- 十一只 - 十一只
Eleven? Eleven puppies, Pongo.
十一只? 十一只小狗, 庞戈 老伙计
Wait a minute now, wait a minute... thirteen!
等等, 等等...十三只!
No, no, no. Fourteen.
不, 不, 不 十四只
- Ohh... fifteen! - Fifteen?
- 哦...十五只! - 十五只?
And the mother's doing fine, love.
而且狗妈妈也很平安, 我亲爱的
You ducky thing, you.
你这幸运的家伙
Fifteen puppies?
十五只小狗?
Why, Pongo, that's marvellous!
啊哈, 庞戈, 这简直太棒了!
It's fabulous!
太不可思议了!
Why, you old rascal!
哈, 你这老家伙!
Fourteen.
十四只
Just fourteen.
只有十四只了
We lost one.
我们失去了一只
Poor little thing.
可怜的小家伙
Oh, Pongo, boy.
唉, 庞戈, 我的老伙计
It's just one of those things.
有时人生就是这样
And yet?
不过?
And yet I wonder.
不过我在想...
Look, Pongo.
瞧, 庞戈
Anita!
安妮塔!
Nanny. Fifteen!
奶妈 十五只!
We still have fifteen!
我们还是有十五只!
Oh, Roger, he's all right! Thank heaven.
哦, 罗杰, 他没事了! 感谢上天
See? He's just as good as new.
看见了? 他就和新的一样
Can you imagine, Roger, fifteen puppies!
你能想像吗, 罗杰 十五只小狗!
Fifteen. Fifteen puppies!
十五只 十五只小狗!
How marvellous.
了不起
How marvellous, how perfectly... ugh!
太了不起了 太好了...哎哟!
The devil take it. They're mongrels... no spots!
见鬼了 这些狗杂种...没斑点的!
No spots at all. What a horrid little white rat.
全都没斑点 白得跟只小老鼠一样
They're not mongrels!
他们不是杂种!
They'll get their spots. Just wait and see.
他们会有斑点的 走着瞧吧
That's right. They'll have their spots in a few weeks.
没错. 只要几个星期他们就会长出斑点的
Oh, well, in that case I'll take them all. The whole litter.
哦, 那好吧, 我全部带走 整个一窝都带走
Just name your price, dear.
开个价吧, 亲爱的
I'm afraid we can't give them up.
恐怕我们不能抛弃他们
Poor Perdita, she'd be heartbroken.
可怜的 佩蒂塔, 她会心碎的
Anita, don't be ridiculous.
安妮塔, 别搞笑了
You can't afford to keep them. You can scarcely feed yourselves.
你不可能负担得起他们的 你连自己都快养不活了
I'm sure we'll get along.
我想我们应付得来
Yes, I know. I know!
是啊是啊, 我知道. 我知道!
Roger's... Roger's songs!
罗杰的... 罗杰的那些歌! 啊哈哈...
Enough of this nonsense. I'll pay you twice what they're worth.
少说废话了 我给你们双倍的价钱好了
I'm being more than generous.
我这人一向慷慨大方
Blast this pen.
这该死的笔
Blast this wretched, wretched pen!
该死的破烂 这倒霉的烂笔!
When can the puppies leave their mother?
什么时候小狗们能离开他们的妈妈?
Two weeks? Three weeks?
两周? 三周?
Never.
永远也不
- What? - We're not selling the puppies.
- 什么? - 我们...我们不卖小狗
Not a single one. Do you understand?
一只也不...不不卖 你听懂了吗?
Anita, is he serious?
安妮塔, 他是认真的嘛?
I really don't know Roger.
我还真有点听不懂 罗杰 说的
- Cruella, he... - Surely he must be joking!
- 克鲁拉, 他好像... - 他一定是在开玩笑!
No, no, no. I mean it.
不, 不不 我我我就是这个意思
You're not getting one. Not one.
你一只也别...别想带走 一...一只也别想
And that's... final.
绝...绝绝对的
Why, you horrid man!
你这混球!
You... you...
你...你们...
All right, keep the little beasts for all I care.
好吧, 留着这些小畜生吧
Do as you like with them. Drown them!
随你们怎么处置它们 全淹死好了!
But I warn you, Anita, I'm through with all of you!
但是我得警告你, 安妮塔 我们绝交了!
I'll get even. Just wait.
我会扳回来的 你们等着吧
You'll be sorry, you fools!
你们会后悔的 你们这些笨蛋!
You... you idiots!
你们这些...你们这些白痴!
Oh, Roger! You were magnificent, darling.
哦, 罗杰! 你表现得那么高尚, 亲爱的
He was a bloomin' hero, ma'am!
他可真是个英雄, 夫人!
Indeed he was. A bloomin' hero!
是个真正的英雄!
Perdy? Perdy, darling?
佩蒂? 佩蒂, 亲爱的?
We're keeping the puppies, every single one of them.
我们可以留住所有的孩子 他们每一个都可以
My ol'pet Roger, he told that devil woman off.
我的老伙计 罗杰 他拒绝了那个坏女人
He told her off, Perdy. She's gone.
他拒绝了她, 佩蒂 她已经走了
- Darling, she's gone for good. - Oh, Pongo.
- 亲爱的, 她走了真好 - 哦, 庞戈.
- C'mon, Thunderbolt. - C'mon, Thunderbolt.
- 加油, 闪电 - 加油, 闪电
Go get him, Thunder.
去逮住他, 闪电
After him, boy.
跟紧他, 伙计
He'll get that dirty ol' horse thief.
他会抓住那个偷马贼的
Old Thunderbolt's the greatest dog in the whole world.
老闪电是世界上最伟大的狗
He's even better than Dad.
他甚至比老爸还强
No dog's better than Dad.
没谁能强过老爸
What's he going to do, Dad?
他打算干什么, 爸爸?
Shh, shh. Let's just wait and see.
嘘, 嘘 接着往下看就知道了
Look at him run, the old coward.
瞧啊他跑了 这胆小鬼
That old dirty Dawson!
这老家伙 道森!
The yellow-livered old skunk!
这个大混球!
I'd like to tear his gizzard out.
我要把他的喉咙撕开
Why, Patch, where did you ever hear such talk?
怎么, 帕奇, 你在哪儿听到这些话?
Certainly not from your mother.
肯定不是从你妈妈这儿
- Watch out, Thunder. - Don't worry, Penny.
- 小心啊, 闪电 - 别担心, 佩妮
He'll get that yellow-livered...
他会抓住那个混...
Well, he'll get him, all right.
反正, 他会抓住他的
Lucky, get down. We can't see.
拉奇, 快下来 我们看不见了
Mother, make him get down.
妈妈, 让他下来吧
C'mon, Lucky. Down, dear.
来吧, 拉奇 下来吧, 亲爱的
Missed him. Missed him by a mile.
没打着 离他差着好一里呢
I'm hungry, mother. I'm hungry.
我饿了, 妈妈 我饿了
Rolly, you've just had your dinner.
洛里, 你才刚用过午饭
But I am, just the same.
可是我还是饿
I'm so hungry I could eat... a whole elephant.
我饿得都可以吃掉... 一整头大象
Shh!
嘘!
There he is, behind that rock.
他在那儿 躲在石头后面
Oh, dear. He shot poor Thunder.
哦, 不好了 他打中了可怜的闪电
He missed him. Ol' Thunder's pretending... I think.
他没打中他 老闪电是假装的...我想是这样
See? What did I tell you? That's one of his tricks.
瞧? 我怎么跟你说的? 这是他的拿手好戏之一
- Lucky, get do wn. - Ha-ha-ha!
- 拉奇, 下来 - 哈-哈-哈!
I'm hungry, Mother. I really am.
我饿了, 妈妈 我真的饿了
Don't miss next week's episode. Who will triumph?
别错过了下礼拜的剧集 谁会获得胜利?
Ol' Thunder always wins!
老闪电 总是会赢!
And speaking of champions, friends,
说到赢家, 朋友们
Kanine Krunchies is the champion of all dog biscuits.
肯耐昆彻斯 是所有狗饼干中的冠军
Kanine Krunchies can't be beat?
肯耐昆彻斯 饼干最好吃
They make each meal a special treat?
它把每餐都变成美食
Happy dogs are those who eat nutritious Kanine Krunchies?
吃有营养的 肯耐昆彻斯 的狗狗们都快乐
Perdy, we better get these little nippers off to bed...
佩蒂, 我们最好送这些小东西上床去...
if we're going for a... w-a-l-k.
如果待会儿我们要去... 散-步-
- We want to go too, Mother. - Can we, Mother?
- 我们也要去, 妈妈 - 可以吗, 妈妈?
We never get to go.
我们从来都没去过
Come along, children. Bedtime.
跟我来, 孩子们 午睡时间
But we're not a... ...bit sleepy.
可是我们还不想[打哈欠]...睡
We want to go for a walk in the park.
我们就想去公园散个步
- Dad, can we? - Better do as your mother says.
- 爸爸, 好吗? - 最好听你妈妈的话
One, two, three, four...
一, 二, 三, 四...
five, six... seven...
五, 六... 七...
eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen...
八, 九, 十, 十一, 十二, 十三...
I'm not sleepy. I'm hungry.
我不想睡, 我饿
fourteen.
十四
Hmm?
嗯?
Remember, friends, just send five...
记住, 朋友们 只要寄上五...
Lucky, you little rascal, let's go.
拉奇, 你这小淘气 我们走
There they go, Horace, me lad,
他们走了 霍勒斯 伙计
out for their evening constitutional.
每晚雷打不动的习惯
A lovely pair of turtledoves.
活象一对热恋中的斑鸠
Around the corner and off to the park.
转过街角 然后去公园散步
Yeah, I don't like it, Jasper.
哼, 我可不喜欢这么干, 贾斯帕
One more pinch and they'll throw the keys away.
他们可随时都会回来
Come off it, Horace. We're getting plenty of boodle.
闭嘴吧, 霍勒斯 我们已经拿了人家不少钱
Yes, but... I've been thinkin'.
那是不假, 可是... 我在考虑...
You've been thinkin'? I warned you about thinkin'.
你在考虑? 我警告你还是别去考虑
I've got the knob for this job, so let's get on with it.
这儿我说了算 咱们把这事干完拉倒
Ah, nobody home but the little ol' cook.
啊哈, 家里只剩下一个老厨子
You just leave her to ol' Jasper.
把她留给我老 贾斯帕.
He can handle her real diplomatic-like.
对付她可说是小菜一碟
Yeah, but I still don't like it.
是啊, 可是我还是不喜欢这么干
Here, here. Patch, you settle down.
来, 帕奇, 你睡这儿
Oh, dear.
哦, 亲爱的
Go to sleep now. Close your little eyes.
现在睡觉吧 闭上你们的小眼睛
That's a good little one.
这样才叫乖小子
Who do you suppose?
会是谁呀?
Good evening, ma'am.
晚上好, 老太太
We're here to inspect the wiring and the switches.
我们是来检查线路开关的
- We're from the gas company. - Electric, electric.
- 我们是煤气公司的 - 是电力, 电力
Electric company.
电力公司
But we didn't call for any inspection.
可是我们可没有请求什么检查
There's a new act just been passed in Parliament.
这是议会最新通过的新法案
Comes under the heading of
归在"帝国防卫法令"之中
"Defence of the Realm Act".
根据法令上第39项第四款条文
It's for your own safety, ma'am.
这是为了你们的住家安全, 老太太
I don't care whatever it says.
我才不管什么国会法令
You're not coming in here with the Mister and Missus gone.
先生太太都出去了 你们不能进来
Come off it, Ducky. We got no time to palaver.
拉倒吧, 老可爱 我们可没时间跟你扯淡
We got a job to do. Excuse me!
我们有工作要做 得罪了!
What's the matter with you two?
你们两个是怎么一回事?
You got cloth ears? You're not coming in!
你们耳聋了吗? 说了你们不准进来!
She's a regular little tartar, ain't she, Horace?
呵呵, 她可凶悍得紧哪 不是吗, 霍勒斯?
Don't you dare go up there, you long-legged lummox!
你们怎么敢在这里乱来 你们这俩长腿笨伯!
Now I mean it.
我说真的
If you don't get out of this house...
你们再不滚出这栋房子...
I'll call the police, I will.
我就要叫警察了, 我要叫了
Now be off with you, you big weasel!
他们会把你们关起来 大恶棍!
Now you've been gone and done it.
你总算说完了
You've cut me to the quick, lady.
你算是把我给伤透了, 老小姐
Why, I wouldn 't stay here if you asked me.
就算你求我, 我也不会再呆在这儿
Not even for a cup of tea.
就算一杯茶也不行
Horace, me lad, I've got a sneaky suspicion
霍勒斯, 老伙计, 人家可疑心我们啦
we're not welcome here.
我估摸着我们可不太受欢迎哪
Pack up. We're leaving.
打包收工喽
Sharp's the word and quick's the action.
废话要少 动作要快
Let me out! Help!
让我出去! 来人啊!
I'll call the police. Help!
我要叫警察了 来人啊!
Goodnight, Ducky. Ta-ta!
晚安, 老可爱 回见吧!
Those good-for-nothing hoodlums!
这些废物点心无赖流氓!
Electric company. Hmph!
电力公司... 呸!
They're nothing but common sneak thieves.
就是些顺手牵羊的小偷
I'll bet they made off with the good silver.
我敢打赌他们拿着我家的贵重银器 撒丫子就溜了
Why, I bet they took every last...
他们要把这儿偷个精光...
The puppies!
小狗狗!
They're gone! Patch? Lucky? Rolly?
他们不见了! 帕奇? 拉奇? 洛里?
They took the puppies!
他们带走了小狗狗!
Oh... Whatever will I do?
哦... 这可该咋办?
Those scoundrels! They stole the puppies.
恶棍! 他们偷走了小狗狗
Police? Help! The puppies.
警察? 救救我的小狗狗
Police! Somebody help me!
警察! 谁来帮帮我!
Help! Help! Help!
来人啊! 帮帮我! 救命啊!
"Dognapping!" Can you imagine such a thing?
"盗狗案!" 会有这种事儿?
"15 puppies stolen". They are darling little things.
"15 只小狗被盗走" 就是那些可爱的小东西
Anita...
安妮塔...
and her bashful Beethoven!
还有她那害羞腼腆的"贝多芬"!
Pipe and all!
吹笛子的家伙!
Oh, Roger, you are a fool!
哈, 罗杰, 你个大笨蛋!
Hello?
喂?
Jasper! Jasper, you idiot!
贾斯帕! 贾斯帕, 你这个白痴!
How dare you call here.
你怎么敢打电话到这里来
We don't want no more of this, we want our boodle!
我们可不想再这样下去了
We'll settle for half!
我们要剩下的酬劳! 把那一半给我们!
Not one schilling 'til the job's done.
这件工作完成以前 我一个子儿也不给!
Jasper! Jasper!
贾斯帕! 贾斯帕!
It's in the blinkin' papers, pictures and all!
这事儿都上报纸头条了 连照片都有!
Hang the papers! It'll be forgotten tomorrow.
别管那些报纸! 明天别人就会忘了这事
- I don't like it. - Shut up, you idiot!
- 我可不喜欢这样 - 闭嘴, 你这白痴!
What?
你说什么?
Not you, miss. I mean Horace!
我不是说你, 小姐 我说 霍勒斯 呢!
Why, you imbecile!
两个低能儿!
Maybe it's Scotland Yard.
没准是苏格兰场(伦敦警察厅)
Maybe they found something. Hello, Inspector?
也许他们发现了什么线索 你好, 警官?
- Is Anita there? - Who?
- 安妮塔 在吗? - 你找谁?
-Anita! - Uh... it's for you.
-安妮塔! - 呃...找你的
Hello?
喂?
Anita, darling. What a dreadful thing.
安妮塔, 亲爱的 多可怕的事呀
I just saw the papers. I couldn't believe it.
我刚看了报纸 真不敢相信
Yes, Cruella. It was quite a shock.
是啊, 克鲁拉 它给我们的打击太大了
- Is she calling to confess? - Roger, please!
- 她打电话来认罪吗? - 罗杰, 别!
- She's a sly one. - We're doing everything possible.
- 她真是个阴谋家 - 我们在尽各种努力
- Have you called the police? - Yes, Scotland Yard.
- 你报了警吗? - 是的, 通知了苏格兰场
- But I'm afraid... - Where are they?
- 可是我担心... - 他们在哪儿?
You idiot!
傻瓜!
- Anita! - Sorry, Cruella.
- 安妮塔! - 不好意思, 克鲁拉.
If there's any news, we'll let you know.
一有消息, 我们会告诉你的
Thank you, Cruella.
谢谢你, 克鲁拉
Roger, I admit she's eccentric, but she's not a thief.
罗杰, 我承认她为人古怪 可是她不会去做贼
Well, she's still number one suspect in my book!
哼, 我还是认为她是头号嫌疑犯!
She's been investigated by Scotland Yard.
苏格兰场已经调查过她了
- What more do you want? - I don't know, darling.
- 你还要想怎么样呢? - 我也不知道, 亲爱的
I don't know.
我不知道啊
Oh, Roger. What'll we do?
唉, 罗杰 我们该怎么办?
What'll we do?
我们该怎么办?
Perdy, I'm afraid it's all up to us.
佩蒂, 我看这事只有靠我们自己了
Oh, Pongo. Isn't there any hope?
哦, 庞戈. 没有任何希望了么?
Well, yes. There's the twilight bark.
有的 试试[黎明之吠]
The twilight bark? That's only a gossip chain.
[黎明之吠]? 那只是个用来闲聊的消息链
Darling, it's the very fastest way to send news.
亲爱的, 它可是最快的消息通道
If our puppies are anywhere in the city,
如果孩子们在城里的某个地方
the London dogs will know.
伦敦的狗们一定能知道
We'll send the word tonight when our pets
今晚我们的宠物带我们去公园散步的时候
take us for a walk in the park.
我们就把这消息发出去
There's no one out tonight. I'm afraid it's too cold.
今晚上太冷了 恐怕没谁会出来
We've got to keep trying, Perdy.
我们得继续试下去, 佩蒂.
Perdy, we're in luck!
佩蒂, 我们真走运!
It's the Great Dane at Hampstead.
那是 汉普斯特德 区的大个子Dane
Quiet, boy!
安静, 伙计!
Do you want to stir up the whole neighbourhood?
你们想把整条街都吵翻吗?
- Perdy, come on! - Let's go.
- 佩蒂, 来吧! - 我们走吧
Pongo, you old idiot!
庞戈, 你这老笨蛋!
Come on, now. We're going home!
给我过来 我们该回家了!
What is it, Danny? Who's on the telegraph?
怎么了, 丹尼? 谁在发消息?
It's Pongo, Regents Park! It's an all-dog alert.
是住在摄政王公园的 庞戈! 那是个全面警报
What's it all about? Tell me, tell me!
到底是什么? 告诉我吧!
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
等一下, 等一下
Well, now... Hmm, that is something.
好了...嗯, 发生了一些事
What, Danny? What's something?
什么, 丹尼? 发生了什么事?
15 Dalmatian puppies, stolen!
15只小斑点狗被盗了!
Have they called the police? Scotland Yard?
他们报了警吗? 苏格兰场呢?
The humans tried everything.
人族已经尽力了
Now it's up to us dogs and the twilight bark.
现在要看我们犬族和[黎明之吠]的力量了
I'll sound the alert!
我要传出这个警报!
Woof! Woof!
汪! 汪!
Ahh!
啊!
Prissy, come in here!
碧西, 这儿来!
Coco!
汪汪!
Be quiet now!
安静点!
Aw, shut up!
噢, 闭嘴!
Quiet!
别吵啦!
Will you be quiet!
你们就不能安静些吗!
Towser, what's going on?
陶瑟尔, 发生什么事了?
What is it? What's all the gossip?
怎么了? 有什么小道消息?
'Taint no gossip, Lucy. It be all the way from London.
不是小道消息, 露西. 是从伦敦传来的
- You don't say! - 15 puppies stolen.
- 怎么说? - 15只小狗被盗
There's no puppies around here, not since Nellie's last litter.
自从内利家生小子以后 这附近可没什么小狗啊
Well, then, we'd best send the word along.
好了, 接下来, 我们最好把这消息往下传
It be up to me to reach the Colonel!
我得通知上校
He be the only one in barking range.
他是唯一一个 在我的吠声范围内的
You'll never reach him at this hour!
这个时候你找不着他的!
Well, I can try!
嗯, 我来试试!
I'll bark all night if I have to.
如果必要, 我就吼他一晚上
Ahem!
啊咳!
Hmm-hmm-hmm.
嗯哼-嗯哼-嗯哼
Hmm... sounds like old Towser.
嗯...听起来象是老陶瑟尔
It's an alert. Sergeant!
是个警报 中士!
Sergeant Tibs! I say, Sergeant!
提比斯中士! 叫你哪, 中士!
Oh, yes, Captain!
哦, 到, 上尉!
Barking signal. It's an alert. Report to the Colonel at once.
收到犬吠信号警报 立即向上校报告
Righto, sir. Right away, sir!
遵命, 长官 立即出发, 长官!
Colonel?
上校?
I say, Colonel! Colonel, sir?
我说, 上校! 上校, 长官?
- Colonel? - What? Who goes there?
- 上校? - 啥? 谁呀?
Sergeant Tibs reporting, sir.
提比斯中士向您报告, 长官
Tibs? Tibs? Oh, yes, Sergeant Tibs!
提比斯? 提比斯? 哦, 是你啊, 提比斯中士!
Look here, Tibs. What's the idea of barging in at this hour?
你瞧你, 提比斯 这个时候打扰我睡觉干嘛?
But Colonel...
可是上校...
Hold on, Sergeant. You hear that?
慢着, 中士 你听见了么?
- Sounds like an alert. - Yes, Colonel.
- 听来象是个警报 - 是的, 上校.
We'd better look into it. Come along, on the double.
我们应该去检查一下. 开步走
Righto, sir.
遵命, 长官.
It's old Towser down at Withermarsh, sir.
那是威瑟马什村的老陶瑟尔, 长官
By Jove, yes! So it is.
没错, 是他
Well, I'll see what he wants.
好, 我来瞧瞧他想干啥
Ahem!
啊咳!
Woof, woof, woof!
汪, 汪, 汪!
It be the Colonel. The old boy himself!
正是上校这个老家伙
He wants the message.
他想知道这个消息
You'd better make it loud or he'll never get it.
你最好大声点, 不然他听不见
One long howl, two short.
一声长啸, 两声短啸
- One yip and a woof. - Two yips, sir.
- 一个尖声和一个粗声 - 是两个尖声, 长官
- What's the word? - It's from London.
- 说的什么? - 是从伦敦传来的
- It must be important. - Yes, I'll get the rest of it.
- 那一定很重要 - 是啊, 我把剩下的接收完
Ahem!
啊咳!
Woof, woof, woof!
汪, 汪, 汪!
[Distant Barking]
[远远的吠声]
Sounds like a number. Three fives is 13.
听来象是个数字 三五一十三
- That's 15, sir. - Of course, 15.
- 是十五, 长官 - 啊对, 十五
[Barking]
[吠声]
Yes... Dot, Spot... Spotted puddings.
是...点, 斑点... 斑点布丁?
Poodles.
小哈巴狗?
- No, puddles! - Puddles, sir?
- 不, 是小狗! - 是小狗, 长官?
15 spotted puddles stolen? Oh, balderdash!
15只斑点狗被盗了? 嘿, 胡说八道!
Better double-check it, Colonel.
还是复查一下为好, 上校
Oh, yes, I suppose I'd better.
嗯, 对 我想也是
Woof, woof, woof!
汪, 汪, 汪!
Two woofs, one yip and a woof.
两个粗声 一个尖声和一个粗声
- It sounds like "puppies"! - Of course, puppies!
- 听起来好像是"小狗狗"! - 对了, 小狗狗!
I just remembered.
我想起来了
Two nights past, I heard puppy barking at Hell Hall.
两天前的夜里, 我听到有小狗叫声从鬼堡里传出来
The old de Vil place? Nonsense, Tibs!
那个老德威尔家族的领地? 瞎说, 提比斯!
No one's lived there for years.
那里有很多年没人住了
Hold on! There's smoke coming from the chimney!
慢着! 那儿的烟囱里有冒烟!
By Jove, that's strange... strange indeed.
有情况...一定有情况
I suppose we'd better investigate.
我看我们需要侦察一下
I'll send word for ol' Towser to stand by.
我会发消息给老陶瑟尔让他等着
Roof! Roo-roo-roof!
汪! 汪汪汪!
Please... stand... by.
请...稍...候
- What's he mean by that? - I don't know.
- 他这是什么意思? - 我不知道
Oh... maybe the ol' boy's found something!
嗯...说不准这老伙计发现了什么!
Oh, I do hope so.
哦, 希望是这样
They say the ol' place is haunted or bewitched or some such fiddle faddle.
有人说这老房子闹鬼还是有巫婆什么的
Fiddle faddle and rot, sir.
闹鬼的烂房子, 长官
Just the same, Sergeant, use extreme caution.
管它呢, 中士 你得加倍小心
No telling what sort of hocus pocus you might run in to.
谁知道里面会有什么麻烦
Blast it all, Tibs. On the double, man.
别管这些了, 提比斯 开步走, 大兵
- On the double. - Yes, sir. Right away, sir.
- 跑步前进 - 遵命, 长官. 立即出发, 长官
Psst!
嘿!
- Rover! Spotty! - Hmm. What?
- 小家伙! 小斑点! - 嗯. 什么?
Are you one of the 15 stolen puppies?
你是那15个被偷来的小狗狗里的一个吗?
We're not stolen. We're bought and paid for.
我们不是被偷来的 我们是被花钱买来的
There's 99 of us all together.
我们99个一起
Ninety-nine!
九十九!
How 'bout that bunch of little ones?
那一群小家伙呢?
They have names and colours. They're not from the pet shops.
他们都有名字和项圈 他们不是从宠物店来的
- Fifteen of 'em. - We never counted them.
- 他们是十五个? - 我们没数过他们
They 're overthere by the tv.
他们都围在电视前面
- I'd better count 'em. - Watch out for the baduns.
- 我来数数 - 小心坏蛋
Baduns?
坏蛋?
Those two blokes, Horace and Jasper.
那两个家伙, 霍勒斯 和 贾斯帕
They 're mean ones, they are.
他们是一伙的
Hey, look, Horace!
嘿, 瞧着, 霍勒斯!
Watch me pot His Lordship smack on the conk.
瞧我怎么射中这贵族老爷的鼻子
Ha-ha-ha-ha. How's that for callin' 'em, eh?
哈-哈-哈-哈 这一下怎么样?
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
哈-哈-哈-哈!
One... two...
一...二...
- three, four, five, six... - Hey, Jasper.
- 三, 四, 五, 六... - 嘿, 贾斯帕.
Give us a swig,
给我留点儿吧
- just a short one. - Now, Horace,
- 就喝一小口 - 拉倒, 霍勒斯
this hogwash ain't fit for a fancy bloke like yourself.
这玩意可不适合你这个烂人
Besides, you'd get crumbs in it, you cabbage head!
再说, 你这猪头一吃喝上就没完!
All right.
好吧
Guzzle the whole works. I hope it gives you colly wobbles, that's what.
你就灌你的马尿吧 喝死你拉倒
Hey, Jasper. Did you...
嘿, 贾斯帕, 你是不是...
Six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven...
六, 七, 八, 九, 十, 十一...
Hey, get down, you runt! Andstay down!
嘿, 滚下来, 小狗崽子! 给我呆着别动!
Go on, get out of here...
滚开...
or I'll black your other peeper.
不然我就臭揍你一顿
Where was I? Nine...
我数到哪儿了? 九...
Nine... three more.
九...这儿三只
Twelve and... one, two, three. That's fifteen!
十二...再加一, 二, 三 正好十五只!
They're the ones!
是他们!
Blimey!
啊呀!
What the...
什么玩意...
Horace, look what we got! A tabby cat!
霍勒斯, 瞧这儿有什么! 一只老猫!
Ha-ha-ha! Ho-ho-ho!
哈-哈-哈! 呵-呵-呵!
How'd you like a tabby cat stew?
你是喜欢吃炖老猫?
Or a cat casserole?
还是吃蒸猫肉?
A la mode!
小样你哪儿跑!
- What is it, Pongo? What is it? - It's the Great Dane.
- 怎么样, 庞戈? 怎么样? - 是大个子Dane.
He has news for us. He'll meet us at Primrose Hill.
他有消息给我们 他让我们在樱草岗上和他见面
- How'll we get out? - The back bedroom window.
- 我们怎么出去呢? - 从卧室的后窗户走
It's always open a wee bit. C'mon.
那里总是会留一个小缝 走吧
Woof! Woof!
汪! 汪!
Pongos, you've made it. Good.
庞戈夫妇, 你们来了 太好了
What's the word? What's the news?
怎么说? 有什么消息?
Have they found our puppies?
有谁找到我们的孩子了吗?
They've been located somewhere north of here...
他们就在这里往北的一个地方...
- in Suffolk. - Oh, thank heaven.
- 在萨福克 - 哦, 上天保佑
- Can you leave tonight? - We can leave right away.
- 你们今晚可以动身吗? - 我们现在就可以动身
I'll go along as far as Camden Road and give you instructions.
我可以把你们一直带到卡姆登路上
When you reach Withermarsh, contact old Towser.
等你们到了威瑟马什村, 就和老陶瑟尔联系
He'll direct you to the Colonel and the Colonel will take you...
他会把你们送到上校那儿 然后上校会带你们到...
to your puppies at the de Vil place.
你们孩子所在的 德威尔 家族领地去
- De Vil! - The de Vil place!
- 德威尔! - 德威尔家族领地!
Oh, Pongo, it was her!
哦, 庞戈, 就是她!
Oh, someone you know?
哦, 你们知道这个名字?
There's no time to explain.
抱歉, 没时间解释了
I hope we're not too late.
希望我们不会来得太晚了
Good luck, Pongo.
祝你好运, 庞戈
If you lose your way, contact the barking chain.
如果你们迷路了 就用吠声来呼叫
They'll be standing by!
他们会等着你们的!
Any news, Colonel?
有消息么, 上校?
Not a blasted thing.
啥也没有
They're lost or captured, or something or other.
庞戈夫妇是走失了, 还是路上被抓走了 还是别的什么
- Who knows what. - Colonel, here comes a car.
- 谁知道呢 - 上校, 来了辆小汽车
Come now, Tibs. Don't be ridiculous.
好啦, 提比斯 别大惊小怪的
- They wouldn't be driving. - Yes, I know, sir.
- 他们俩又不会开车来 - 是啊, 我知道, 长官
But it's heading for Hell Hall.
可是那车往鬼堡开过去了
It... It's stopping at the gate!
它...它停在了大门前!
It is?
有吗?
Blast it all! Better see what's up.
真见鬼! 要去看看怎么回事
- On the double, man. On the double! - Yes, sir.
- 开步走, 伙计们. 开步走! - 是, 长官
Take over, Captain.
现在你接管此处, 上尉
Righto, sir.
遵命, 长官
I'm sorry, MrSimpkins. The answer is no, no, no.
抱歉啦, 辛普金斯先生 回答是:不, 不, 不
Six down, four to go.
过了6关, 还有4关
I've got no time to argue. It's got to be done tonight.
我没时间和你们瞎吵吵 今晚这事儿必须干完
It must be a yes or no question.
这问题必须回答"是"还是"不是"
Do you understand? Tonight!
你们听懂了吗? 今晚上!
But they ain 't big enough.
可是这些小狗还小着吶
You couldn't get half a dozen coats out of the whole caboodle.
这一堆小狗还不够做半打外套的
Coats! Dog-skin coats?
外套! 狗皮外套?
We'll settle for half a dozen! We can't wait.
我们就做半打好了! 我们不能再等下去了
The police are everywhere. I want the job done tonight!
警察到处出动 今晚上这活儿就得做掉!
How're we gonna do it?
可我们怎么做呢?
Any way you like. Poison them, drown them.
随便你们怎么干 毒死它们, 淹死它们
Bash them in the head. You got any chloroform?
狠打它们的头 你们有麻醉剂吗?
- Not a drop. - And no ether, "ee-ther".
- 一滴都没有 - 也没有"吉他"的
"Eye-ther"!
是"其它"!
I don't care how you kill the little beasts,
我才不管你们怎么杀掉这些小畜生
but do it... and do it now!
只要现在就给我做!
Aw, please, miss. Have pity.
嗨, 求你了, 小姐 可怜可怜吧
Can't we see the rest of the show first?
先让我们看完这电视秀吧?
We want to see "What's My Crime?"
我们想看完这个"我犯的啥罪?"节目
Listen, you idiots!
好好听着, 你们这俩白痴!
I'll be back in the morning. The job better be done...
明早我就会回来 要么这活儿干完了...
or I'll... I'll call the police!
要么我就... 我就叫警察了!
Do you understand?
你们懂了吗?
I think she means it.
我觉得她是说真的
Ah... We'll get on with it...
啊...我们会干活的...
as soon as the show's over.
等这节目一结束就干
Will you please sign in, sir?
请你签在这里好么, 先生?
You'd better get out of here if you want to save your skins.
你们最好马上离开这儿 如果你们还想留着这身皮的话
- But how? - Shh.
- 可是怎么出去呢? - 嘘
There's a hole in the wall there by the door.
那边墙上有个洞 靠门的那个
C'mon, shake a leg.
来呀, 撒丫子溜吧
Psst. Kids, follow me.
孩子, 跟我来
Hey, Jasper, look! Ha-ha-ha-ha.
嘿, 贾斯帕, 瞧啊! 哈哈哈哈
It's old Meathead.
是这个笨蛋啊
Yeah, what do you know... old Meathead Fauncewater.
哪, 你猜怎么着... 是老笨蛋范斯沃特
C'mon, don't crowd.
慢慢来, 别挤着
One at a time. One at a time!
一次一个 一次过一个!
For our last contestant,
现在是我们的最后来宾
meet Mr Percival Fauncewater.
珀西瓦尔 范斯沃特先生
If the panel fails to guess your
如果在10个问题里
unusual crime in ten questions,
审判团还推测不到你的不寻常的犯罪行为
you will receive two weeks vacation at a seaside resort,
你将获得为期两周的海滨度假作为奖励
all expenses paid.
费用全免
That is, after you've paid your debt to society.
当然, 是在你偿还完你对社会的债务之后
Who will take the first question? Inspector?
谁来问第一个问题? 检察官?
Could your crime be classified as larceny?
你的犯罪可以被归类到 "盗窃罪"一类么?
-A theft, burglary? - Straighten out!
- 一种偷盗, 入室行窃? - 走直线啊孩子们!
Form a queue... along the wall. Snap it up.
排成队...贴着墙走 抓紧时间啊
Mr Fauncewater is a burglarby trade,
范斯沃特先生是一个夜贼惯偷
but in this case, his crime was not burglary.
不过在这件案子里 他的罪行可不是入室行窃
The answer is no.
回答是"不"
One down, nine to go. Miss Birdwell?
过了1关, 还有9关 伯维尔小姐?
If your crime wasn't robbery, did you...
如果你的罪行不是抢掠, 那么你...
Oh, dear, what I mean is...
哦, 亲爱的 我的意思是...
Do something of a violent nature, that is...
根据人性本恶的规律, 那就是...
Come, Miss Birdwell, we're running short of time.
哎呀, 伯维尔小姐 我们的时间可不多了
So sorry.
真抱歉
- Did you do someone in? - Oh!
- 那么你是否造成对别人的伤害? - 哦!
I'm sorry. The answer is no.
抱歉了 回答是"不"
Two down, eight to go.
过了2关 还有8关
- Mr Simpkins? - Psst.
- 辛普金斯先生? - 嘘
Hey, kid, let's go.
- 嘿, 小子, 走吧 - 如果不是抢掠也不是伤害
Could it be a violation of a city ordinance?
那是否是违反公共秩序之类?
No.
不是
Hey, get out of the way, you little runt!
嘿, 滚开吧, 你个小畜生!
Three down, seven to go. Inspector?
过了3关 还有7关. 检察官?
Very confusing, I must say.
我不得不承认 这很让人迷惑
Surely, this crime could...
很显然, 这罪行也许...
I'm terribly sorry.
我十分抱歉
-We've run out of time. - Ain't that always the way!
- 我们得抓紧时间了 - 真是的, 每次都这样!
Would it be possible for Mr Fauncewater to come back next week?
能否请范斯沃特先生下周再来?
Then we could finish our little game.
然后我们再完成这个小游戏呢
Goodnight, audience. See you next week at this same time...
晚安, 观众朋友们 下周同样时间请继续观赏...
on "What's My Crime?"
"我犯的啥罪?"节目
Ah, oh well.
呵, 好了
C'mon, Horace. Let's get on with it.
来吧, 霍勒斯 来干活吧
I'll pop 'em on the head, you do the skinnin'.
我来敲头 你来剥皮
No you don't, Jasper!
我才不呢, 贾斯帕!
I'll pop 'em off and you do the skinnin'.
我来敲头 你来剥皮
Horace, look!
霍勒斯, 瞧那儿!
They're gone. They flew the coop...
它们都跑了...
right out through this hole. Here, grab a torch.
就是从这个洞里逃走的 赶紧拿个手电来
We'll run 'em down before you can say "Bob's your uncle".
趁事儿闹大发之前 我们得马上去把它们追回来
There they go, Horace, up the stairs.
它们在那儿, 霍勒斯 上楼
Here puppies.
来啊小狗狗
Here, puppies! C'mon now.
来, 小狗狗! 到这儿来
Don't go hiding from ol' Uncle Jasper.
别跟老叔叔贾斯帕玩捉迷藏啦
I ain't gonna hurt ya.
我不会伤害你们的
I thought we was gonna pop 'em off.
不是说我们要把它们都打死么
Shut up. Take a squint in there.
闭嘴吧 在这儿守好了
I'll check these other two rooms.
我到那两个房间去查查
Here, puppies.
小狗狗
Come on out. Come out wherever you are.
出来吧 都出来吧
Horace! Oh!
霍勒斯! 哦!
It's that mangy tabby cat. He's the ringleader.
是那只老脏猫 它就是罪魁祸首
Head 'em off. Head 'em...
捉住它们 捉住它...
You bungling blockhead!
你这笨手笨脚的傻瓜!
Back here! Back here!
躲这儿来! 躲这儿来!
Shh. Here they come.
嘘 他们来了
Double-crossin 'little twerps, pullin 'a snitch on us!
都是你碍手碍脚!
After we took care of 'em. There's gratitude for you.
等我们抓住了它们 再和你算帐
It ain't fair, Jasp er.
这不公平, 贾斯帕.
Horace, there they go!
霍勒斯, 它们在那儿!
Sergeant? I say, Sergeant.
中士? 叫你哪, 中士
No time to explain. Busy, sir.
没时间解释了 忙着逃命哪, 长官
Shut that door!
关门, 霍勒斯!
We'll close in on 'em. Enough of this "Ring Around the Rosy".
我们关起门来打狗 它们逃不了啦
Oh, Pongo, I'm afraid we're lost.
哦, 庞戈 恐怕我们迷路了
It can't be far.
不会很远了
By Jove! It can't be the Pongos.
老天爷! 该不会是庞戈夫妇吧
Grrr...
嗝...
It's the Colonel. This way.
是上校 走这边
Colonel? Are you the Colonel?
上校? 你是上校吗?
Oh, Pingo! Uh... Uh... Pongo?
哦, 是平戈嘛! 呃...呃...是庞戈?
Our puppies, are they all right?
我们的孩子 他们都还好吗?
No time to explain. There's trouble.
没时间多说了 有麻烦了
A big hullabaloo. Come along!
好大的喧哗声 快来!
Follow me!
跟我来!
Ah, ha-ha-ha!
啊哈哈哈!
Now we've got 'em, Horace. They 've run out of room.
现在可逮着它们了, 霍勒斯 它们哪儿也逃不了了
What have we got here? A couple of spotted hyenas?
这是什嘛玩意? 一对斑点土狼?
C'mon, Horace. Give 'em what for.
上, 霍勒斯 给它们点厉害瞧瞧
I'm right behind ya, lad.
你上我掩护, 伙计
Uh... oh!
呃...哦!
You clumsy clod!
你个土块脑瓜!
I'll knock the spots off you. Let go!
我要揍扁了你们 上啊!
Let go!
上啊!
Well, by George!
老天爷!
You mangy mongrel!
你个癞皮狗杂种!
I'll knock your blinkin 'block off.
我要宰了你!
Yeow!
呦-嗷!
Blast 'em, Tibs. Give 'em what for.
上啊, 提比斯 来修理他们一顿
No, Colonel. Retreat, retreat!
不要, 上校 该撤退, 撤退!
Yes. Yes, of course. Retreat!
对啊. 对啊, 没错 撤退!
Retreat, on the double!
立即撤退!
Help, Jasper! Get me out of here!
救命啊, 贾斯帕! 来救救我啊!
Horace, they're fighting dirty!
霍勒斯, 它们咬得可凶呢!
Oh, oh, oh!
哦, 哦, 哦!
Oh, oh, oh! Jasper!
哦, 哦, 哦! 贾斯帕!
Horace!
霍勒斯!
C'mon, Perdy. Let's go.
来啊, 佩蒂 我们走
I'll skin every one of them spotted hyenas...
我要剥了那俩癞皮土狼的皮...
if it's the last thing I do.
哪怕我拼了老命也要做到
Dad! Mother!
爸爸! 妈妈!
- I missed you, Mommy. - Here we are, Mommy.
- 我真想你, 妈咪 - 我们又在一起了, 妈咪
Oh, my darlings... my darlings!
哦, 我的宝贝... 我的宝贝!
- How'd you find us? - Lucky, Patch, Pepper!
- 你们怎么找到我们的? - 拉奇, 帕奇, 佩珀!
Oh, Daddy.
哦, 爸爸
And Rolly, you rascal!
还有洛里, 你这个小淘气!
Did you bring me anything to eat?
你给我带什么吃的了吗?
Everybody here? All 15?
都在这儿了? 15个都在吗?
Twice that many, Dad. Now there's 99 of us!
比2倍还多呢, 爸爸 这儿有99个我们!
What? Nine... 99?
什么? 九...九十九个?
Where did they all come from?
他们都是从哪儿来的?
What would she want with so many?
那女人要这么多孩子想要做什么?
She's gonna make coats out of us.
她想拿我们来做外套
- She couldn't! - That's right, dog-skin coats.
- 天哪! - 是真的, 狗皮外套
Oh, dog-skin coats! Come now, Tibs!
啊, 狗皮外套! 少扯了, 提比斯!
But it's true, sir.
可这是真的, 长官
Horace and Jasper were gonna pop us off
霍勒斯和贾斯帕准备杀掉我们,
and... skin us!
然后...剥我们的皮!
She's a devil, a witch! What'll we do?
她真是一个魔鬼, 一个巫婆! 我们该怎么办?
We have to get back to London somehow.
我们要想办法回伦敦去
What about the others? What'll they do?
其他的孩子怎么办? 他们该怎么办?
Perdy, we'll take them home with us... all of them.
佩蒂, 我们带他们一起回家 所有的孩子一起
Our pets would never turn them out.
我们的宠物们不会赶他们走的
Colonel, sir, lights on the road.
上校先生 路上有光亮
It's a truck headin' this way.
有辆卡车向这边开过来
It's the baduns, Horace and Jasper.
是那些恶棍 霍勒斯和贾斯帕
They 're following our tracks.
他们是顺着我们的脚印追来的
We've got 'em out numbered, Tibs.
我们来对付他们, 提比斯
When I give the signal, we'll attack.
等我发出信号 就开始攻击
Sir, I'm afraid that would be disastrous.
长官, 恐怕那样我们会损失惨重
Ahem! Oh, think so?
啊哦! 嗯, 你也这么想?
We'd better run for it.
他说得对, 上校 我们最好赶紧逃命
Out the back, across the pasture.
从后面走 穿过农场
Thank you sergeant, Colonel, Captain.
多谢你们, 中士 上校, 上尉
- Bless you all. - How can we ever repay you?
- 上帝保佑你们 - 我们该怎么报答你们呢?
Ahem! Nothing at all. All in the line of duty.
啊哈! 什么也不用 保卫同胞是我们的义务
That's right, sir... routine.
说得对, 长官... 例行常事嘛
Better be off. Here they come.
赶紧走吧 他们来了
C'mon, kids, hurry.
来吧, 孩子们, 快点走
- Good luck, Pongos. - And never fear.
- 祝你们好运, 庞戈夫妇 - 别担心
We'll hold them off 'til the bitter end.
我们会阻击他们 至死不休
Now, what's this?
什么呀?
Out of my way, you barkin' haystack.
别挡着我的路 你个乱嚎乱叫的干草堆
Or I'll knock your blinkin' block off!
要不我揍扁了泥泞!
They ain't in here.
它们不在这儿
They're hiding in the hay.
他们没准藏在草堆里
Give me a match. We'll burn 'em out.
给我根火柴 我们把它们烧出来
Ready, Captain. Aim,
预备, 上尉 瞄准
fire one.
第一发
Fire two.
第二发
Hey, there they go, the little sneaks.
嘿, 他们在那儿 这些小狗贼
C'mon, back to the truck. We'll head 'em off in half a mile.
快来, 回到车上去 不出半里路我们就能截住它们
They gotta be around here somewhere.
他们一准在这附近
- I've been thinkin'. - Now, Horace.
- 我正在想呢 - 拉倒吧, 霍勒斯.
What if they went down the froze-up creek...
有没有可能是它们 从结冻的小溪上走...
so 's not to leave their tracks?
所以没留下脚印?
Horace, you idiot!
霍勒斯, 你个白痴!
Dogs ain't that smart.
狗才没那么机灵呢
All clear, Perdy.
安全了, 佩蒂
-All clear. - We gave 'em the slip! Didn't we, Dad?
-没事了 - 我们把他们给耍了! 对吗, 爸爸?
They didn't even see us, Patch!
他们根本没看见我们, 帕奇!
Shh, children. Children, shh.
嘘, 孩子们 孩子们, 嘘
My feet are slippery.
我的脚底直打滑
I wish we could walk on the snow.
我宁可走雪地
No, son, we can't leave tracks.
不行, 孩子, 我们可不能留下脚印
Well, any sign of them?
怎样, 找到它们了么?
Not so much as one bloomin' footprint.
一个梅花脚印都没发现
And we've been up and down every road in the county.
这个地区的每条路我们都跑遍了
We're froze stiff. We're givin' up.
我们快冻僵了. 放弃吧
Oh, no, you don't!
哦, 不行, 不准你们放弃!
We'll find the little mongrels if it takes 'til next Christmas.
我们得找到那些小杂种 哪怕找到明年圣诞
Now get going! Watch your driving!
现在给我上路! 另外开车看着点路!
Do you wanna get nabbed by the police?
你们想让警察逮起来吗?
Ninety-three,
九十三,
ninety-four, ninety-five, ninety-six,
九四 九五 九六
ninety-seven,
九七
ninety-eight...
九八...
Oh, Lucky!
哦, 拉奇!
C'm on, Lucky boy. We can't give up now.
来啊, 拉奇小子 现在可不能放弃
I'm tired and I'm hungry and my tail's froze...
我又累又饿 我的尾巴也冻僵了...
and my nose is froze and my ears are froze.
我的鼻子冻僵了 我的耳朵冻僵了
And my toes are froze.
我的脚趾头也冻僵了
Pongo!
庞戈!
Pongo! Pongo!
庞戈! 庞戈!
We'd just about lost hope. We have shelter for you...
我们差点就绝望了 我们给你们预备了个藏身所...
at the dairy barn across the road.
就在马路对面的挤奶厂
Oh, thank goodness.
哦, 太感谢了
Perdy! Perdy!
佩蒂! 佩蒂!
This way, Perdy.
这边来, 佩蒂
- The dairy barn across the road. - C'mon, kids.
- 到马路对面的挤奶厂去 - 来吧, 孩子们
It's not far. C'mon, this way.
不算远的 来, 走这边
Follow the collie.
跟着这位牧羊犬大叔
Just look, Queenie.
快看哪, 奎尼
Have you ever seen so many puppies?
你可曾见过这么多的小狗狗么?
Aren't they adorable!
他们可真可爱啊!
- Perfectly darling. - The poor dears.
- 太可爱了 - 真是一群小可怜
They 're completely worn out and half frozen!
他们都累坏了 也块冻坏了!
They all here, Pongo?
他们都到齐了么, 庞戈?
Yes, dear. All 99 accounted for.
是的, 亲爱的. 我点过99个都在
The famous Pongos. We were so worried about you.
原来是闻名的庞戈夫妇 我们都很为你们担心呢
Been trying to reach you. Afraid you'd been captured.
我试着找过你们 还担心你们被抓走了
How did you make it all this way?
你们这一路上可很不容易吧?
And in such dreadful weather.
在这样一个可怕的坏天气里
With all those little ones.
还带了这么多的小毛毛
I'm hungry, Mother. I'm hungry.
我好饿, 妈妈 我饿呀
- I'm hungry too. - Mother, we're hungry.
- 我也饿了 - 妈妈, 我们饿了
- We're all hungry. - I'm sorry, children.
- 我们都饿了 - 真对不起, 孩子们
Do they like warm milk? It's fresh.
他们喜欢喝温牛奶么? 还是新鲜的呢
- Where is it? - Where is the milk?
- 哪里有? - 哪里有牛奶?
Come and get it, kids. It's on the house.
进来喝吧, 孩子们 就在这屋子里
This way, children. Around this way.
走这边, 孩子 走这边来
Don't crowd. You'll have to take turns.
别挤 你们得轮着来
Rolly, wait your turn, dear.
洛里, 等轮到你吧, 亲爱的
Don't worry, kids. There's plenty for all.
别担心, 孩子们 这儿的牛奶管够管饱
Ooh! The little darlings.
噢! 这些小家伙
Pongo, a fews craps I saved...
庞戈, 这儿有点剩饭...
- for you and the missus. - Oh, thank you.
- 是我给你和你夫人留的 - 哦, 多谢你
It's not much, but it might hold you as far as Dinsford.
虽然不太多, 不过应该可以帮你们支撑到丁斯夫.
Huh? Dinsford?
嗯? 丁斯夫?
There's a Labrador there.
那里住着一位拉布拉多猎犬
- His pet is a grocer. - Oh, I... I'm sorry.
- 他的宠物是个杂货商 - 呵, 我...我很抱歉
Quite all right.
没关系, 没关系
Get some rest and don't worry. I'll be standing watch.
尽管休息吧, 别担心 我来放哨
I don't know what we'd have done if...
我真不知道该怎么报答你们...
We're honoured to be of service.
我们很高兴能帮得上忙
We're sorry we can't do more.
只是遗憾不能帮助你们更多
Anyone who would think of hurting these puppies...
谁想伤害这些小狗狗的...
- Shh! Duchess! - They're so dear.
- 嘘! 公爵夫人! - 他们需要休息
I wish they could stay with us for always.
我好希望他们能留下来陪伴我们
Princess, shh. Quiet, everyone.
公主, 嘘 大家都安静
Let them sleep, the poor things.
让他们好好睡一觉 这些可怜的小家伙
They're so exhausted and they still have such a long way to go.
他们都给累坏了 而且他们还有很长的路要走呢
Hurry, kids. Hurry!
赶紧走, 孩子们. 快点!
Well now, what have we here?
哼哼, 看看这是什么?
Well... so they thought they could outwit Cruella.
哼...它们以为能瞒得过我克鲁拉
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
哈哈哈哈!
Jasper! Horace!
贾斯帕! 霍勒斯!
Here's their tracks heading for the village.
这是它们往那村子去的脚印
Blimey! It's them, all right.
啊呀! 就是它们
Work your way south on the side roads. I'll take the main road.
你们从南边的那条路搜过去 我从这条主道过去
See you in Dinsford!
在丁斯夫里碰头!
Pongo, I've got a ride home for you.
庞戈, 我给你们准备了一趟返程车
A ride home? Perdy, did you hear that?
返程车? 佩蒂, 你听见了吗?
- For all of us? - You mean we don't have to walk any more?
- 给我们大家的? - 你是说我们不用再步行了?
If we can manage it. We'd better hurry.
如果一切顺利的话 来吧, 我们得快点
We've got a ride home! C'mon, children.
我们可以坐上返程车! 快来, 孩子们
See the van down the street?
看见停在街上的那辆大蓬货车了吗?
It's going to London as soon as the engine's repaired.
它是去伦敦的 引擎一修好就走
And there's room for all of you.
上面可以藏下你们一大家子
Pongo, there's Cruella.
庞戈, 那是克鲁拉
Yes...
是啊...
and Jasper and Horace.
还有贾斯帕和霍勒斯
How will we get to the van?
我们怎么靠近那大蓬货车呢?
I don't know, Perdy.
我不知道, 佩蒂
- But somehow we've got to. - Mother, Dad,
- 可我们一定得上去 - 妈妈, 爸爸
- Patch pushed me in the fireplace. - Lucky pushed me first.
- 帕奇推我到壁炉里 - 拉奇先推我的
- Did not. Did not. - Did too. Did too.
- 才没有. - 就有
Did not!
就没有!
- Please, children, don't quarrel. - Say...
- 孩子们, 不能吵嘴 - 这么说...
Perdy, I've got an idea.
佩蒂, 我有主意了
Pongo,
庞戈
- what on earth... - Look, I'm a Labrador!
- 这是怎么了... - 瞧啊, 我变成一个拉布拉多猎犬了!
We 'll all roll in soot. We 'll be Labradors.
我们都跳进煤灰里 我们就都是拉布拉多猎犬
Say, that is an idea!
嘿, 这是个好主意!
C'mon, kids! Roll in the soot.
来吧, 孩子们! 都跳到煤灰里来
You mean, you want us to get dirty?
你是说, 你要我们弄脏自己?
Did you hear that, Freckles? Dad wants us to get dirty.
你们听见了吗, 雀斑? 爸爸要我们把自己弄脏
- Mother, should we? - Do as your father says.
- 妈妈, 我们可以去么? - 照你爸爸说的做吧
- This'll be fun. - I always wanted to get good and dirty.
- 这可太有趣了 - 我一直都想这么干
That's the stuff. The blacker the better.
就是这样, 越黑越好
- I'm ready. - Me too.
- 我好了 - 我也是
How's this, Dad?
这一下怎么样, 爸爸?
Wait. That's enough. Not too many at a time.
等等. 够了. 一次别太多了
Uh-oh. Rolly, hold on. You're only half done.
啊哦. 洛里, 慢着 你只做了一半
Now, stay right with me.
从现在起, 紧紧跟着我
We're gonna fool the ol' mad lady.
我们要去耍耍那个老疯婆子
Pongo...
庞戈...
I'm so afraid.
我真害怕
Jasper, do you suppose they disguised themselves?
贾斯帕, 你觉得它们会伪装自己么?
Say now, Horace. That's just what they did.
瞧着吧, 霍勒斯 它们就是这么干的
Dogs is always paintin' themselves black!
狗就是喜欢把自己涂成黑的!
You idiot!
你这白痴!
Well, so far so good.
嗯, 到目前为止还算顺利
C'mon, Perdy. Better get on your make-up.
来吧, 佩蒂 来把你自己也装扮一下
I'll go ahead with the next bunch.
我来带领下一拨
Jasper! Horace!
贾斯帕! 霍勒斯!
- Well? - Be reasonable, miss.
- 怎样? - 发发慈悲吧, 小姐
We're froze to our bones.
我们骨头都冻僵了
We've been out all night and all day, with nothin' to eat.
我们忙了整天整夜 一口吃的都没
They're somewhere in this village, and we're going to find them.
它们就在这村子里 我们要找到它们
Now get going!
给我继续找!
Do you think they've seen us?
你觉得他们看见我们了吗?
No, but we're running out of time.
不会, 可是我们得抓紧时间了
Try 'er again, mate.
再试试, 伙计
Hurry, Perdy. The van's about to leave.
快, 佩蒂 大货车要开走了
Better hurry.
赶快
I'll get the rest.
我去接剩下的
That ought to do. She'll get you back to London.
这下应该可以了 她能把你们带回伦敦
Better get aboard, miss.
赶紧上车, 女士
Hey, Jasper.
嘿, 贾斯帕
C'mon, Horace.
来啊, 霍勒斯
Hurry, kids!
快来, 孩子们!
C'mon, kids. Run on ahead.
快, 孩子们 往前跑
- She's watching us, Dad. - Keep going.
- 她盯着我们呢, 爸爸 - 别停下
It can't be!
不会吧!
It's impossible!
这不可能!
Run for it!
赶紧逃呀!
-Jasper! Horace! - [Honking]
-贾斯帕! 霍勒斯! - [鸣喇叭]
Jasper!
贾斯帕!
There they go... in the van.
它们跑了... 在那货车上
After them! After them!
追上它们! 追上它们!
Pongo! There she is... Cruella.
庞戈! 她追上来了...是克鲁拉
Hey, lady,
嘿, 女士
what in thunder are you tryin' to do?
你搞什么鬼?
Crazy woman driver!
乱开车的疯婆子!
- Pongo, look! - Jasper!
- 庞戈, 看! - 贾斯帕!
Ain't nothin' to it.
它们跑不了啦
I'll give him a nudge and shove him in the dirt.
我要把他们挤到泥巴地里去
Perdy, watch out!
佩蒂, 当心啊!
- Jasper! - Horace!
- 贾斯帕! - 霍勒斯!
You idiots!
你个白痴!
You fools!
你个笨蛋!
You imbeciles!
你个低能!
Ah, shut up!
啊, 闭嘴吧!
Roger, after all, that's your first big hit.
罗杰, 毕竟这是你第一首畅销曲
It's made more money than we ever dreamed of.
它替我们赚到了从未想过会拥有的钱
Yes, I know.
对, 我知道
I still can't believe...
我就是不能相信...
that Pongo and Perdy would run away.
庞戈和佩蒂会离家出走
Here's a bit of Christmas cheer for you,
这个圣诞节假如还有什么事值得高兴一下
If there's anything to be cheerful about.
那就剩这个了
Oh, those dear little things.
唉, 那些可爱的小东西
Sometimes at night I can hear them barking,
有时候我在夜里都听见他们的叫声
but it always turns out I'm dreaming.
可那都是我的梦而已
Roger, what on earth...
罗杰, 这怎么回事...
They're Labradors.
他们是拉布拉多猎犬
No, no. They're covered with soot.
不, 不是 他们是被煤灰染的
Look, here's Lucky!
看哪, 是拉奇!
Pongo, boy, is that you?
庞戈, 小伙子 是你吗?
Oh, Pongo, Pongo! Ho-ho, it's Pongo!
哦, 庞戈, 庞戈! 呵呵, 是庞戈!
And Perdy, my darling.
还有佩蒂, 我亲爱的
And Patch, and Rolly,
还有帕奇, 还有洛里
and Penny, and Freckles.
还有佩妮, 还有雀斑
They're all here, the little dears.
他们都回来了 这些小可爱
- It's a miracle! - What a wonderful Christmas present!
- 真是个奇迹! - 多奇妙的圣诞礼物啊!
And look... there's a whole lot more!
看哪... 那儿还有更多!
Look, Anita, puppies everywhere.
看, 安妮塔, 到处都是小狗
There must be 100!
肯定有一百只!
One, two, three and four... is seven.
一 二 三 四...七只
Two, four, six, and three is nine,
二 四 六, 还有三只 这里九只,
plus two is eleven.
再加这两只是十一只
- 36 over here. - 36 and 11, that's 47!
- 这儿有三十六只 - 三十六加十一, 那就是四十七只!
- Eighteen, Roger. - That's 65!
- 我这儿十八只, 罗杰 - 那是六十五只!
Ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen!
十 十一 十二 十三!
- Wait... six more. - Let's see, that's 84.
- 等等...还有六只 - 那么就是八十四只
And fifteen plus two... a hundred and one!
再加十五只还有两只...一零一只!
A hundred and one? Where did they come from?
一零一? 它们都是从哪儿来的?
Oh, Pongo, you old rascal!
哦, 庞戈, 你这老家伙!
- What'll we do with them? - We'll keep'em.
- 我们把他们怎么办呢? - 我们收留他们吧
- In this little house? - We'll buy a big place in the country.
- 在这栋小房子里? - 我们可以买一栋大房子
We'll have a plantation... a Dalmatian plantation.
我们可以办一所养殖场... 一个斑点狗大养殖场
Roger, that's truly an inspiration.
罗杰, 这真是个好主意
It'll be a sensation!
一定会很轰动!
We'll have a Dalmatian plantation.
我们要办一个养殖场
A Dalmatian plantation, I say.
一个斑点狗养殖场